export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "What is used in ReactJs to increase performance?",
        optionA: "Both B and C",
        optionB: "Original DOM",
        optionC: "Virtual DOM",
        optionD: "None of the above",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "React is a",
        optionA: "Javascript library",
        optionB: "Javascript framework",
        optionC: "Both of above",
        optionD: "None of above",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of this is not a javascript framework?",
        optionA: "React",
        optionB: "Angular",
        optionC: "Vue",
        optionD: "Java",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "React is",
        optionA: "Component based",
        optionB: "Module based",
        optionC: "Both of above",
        optionD: "None of above",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of this is not a programming language?",
        optionA: "Python",
        optionB: "JavaScript",
        optionC: "MC-03",
        optionD: "Java",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Number of elements, a valid react component can return",
        optionA: "1",
        optionB: "2",
        optionC: "3",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "State in react is",
        optionA: "A permanent storage",
        optionB: "Internal storage of the component",
        optionC: "Both of above",
        optionD: "None of above",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Props in react can",
        optionA: "Be changed inside the component",
        optionB: "Not be changed in the component",
        optionC: "Be changed in side other component",
        optionD: "None of above",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "HTML stands for",
        optionA: "HyperText Markup Language",
        optionB: "HyperText and links Markup Language",
        optionC: "HyperText Markup Language",
        optionD: "None of these",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",
        optionA: "<pre>",
        optionB: "<a>",
        optionC: "<b>",
        optionD: "<br>",
        answer: "C",
    }
];